lids.com 2007-04-03

# Lids.com: Lids Online has an extensive selection of hats, apparel and accessories for your favorite teams

|  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---  
| SHOP BY  
  
|  |   
---|---|---  
| YOUR TEAM  
  |   
  |   
  |   
  |   
  |   
  |   

|    
|  | 

|   
---  
  
  * [What is the lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ safe shopping guarantee?](http://www.lids.com/privacy_policy.html/#guarantee)
  * [What personal information about customers does lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ gather?](http://www.lids.com/privacy_policy.html/#personal)
  * [Does lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ share the information it receives?](http://www.lids.com/privacy_policy.html/#share)
  * [Do lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ collect information from children?](http://www.lids.com/privacy_policy.html/#children)
  * [What are the conditions of use, notices, and revisions for the lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ web site?](http://www.lids.com/privacy_policy.html/#revisions)
  * [What is the lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ fraud prevention statement?](http://www.lids.com/privacy_policy.html/#fraud)

PRIVACY & SECURITY  
lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting lids.com™ and hatworld.com™, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.  
What is the lids.com™ and hatworld.com™safe shopping guarantee?  ( [Top](http://www.lids.com/privacy_policy.html#top) )  
The lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ Safe Shopping Guarantee protects you while you shop at lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ so that you never have to worry about credit card safety. We guarantee that every transaction you make at lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ will be safe. This means that you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your card as a result of shopping at lids.com™ and hatworld.com™

Guarantee Details:

  1. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50, lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50. lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ will cover this liability only if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made at lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ while using the secure server.
  2. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.
  3. Our liability if unauthorized charges are made to your card as a result of shopping at lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ is limited to $50 or the lesser amount for which your bank holds you liable. We are not liable for any incidental or consequential damages you may incur in connection with the unauthorized charges or for any amount in excess of $50 that your bank may require you to pay because you failed to comply with the bank's rules and procedures concerning the unauthorized charge.

What personal information about customers does lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ gather?  ( [Top](http://www.lids.com/privacy_policy.html#top) )  
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at lids.com™ and hatworld.com™. Here are the types of information we gather:

  * Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. Scroll to the bottom of this page to see examples of what we collect. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.
  * Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies" and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses lids.com™ and hatworld.com™.Scroll to the bottom of this page to see examples of the information we receive. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.
  * E-mail Communications: To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please notify us by sending an e-mail to [contactus@hatworld.com](mailto:contactus@hatworld.com).
  * Information from Other Sources: For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (for example, providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.

What about cookies?  ( [Top](http://www.lids.com/privacy_policy.html#top) )  
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.

The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.  
  
Does lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ share the information it receives?  ( [Top](http://www.lids.com/privacy_policy.html#top) )  
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and **we are not in the business of selling information about our customers to others**. We share information only within the group of companies controlling, under common control with, or controlled by Hat World, Inc..

  * Agents: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
  * Promotional Offers: Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers, please notify us by sending an e-mail to [contactus@hatworld.com](mailto:contactus@hatworld.com).
  * Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that lids.com™ and hatworld.com™, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
  * Protection of lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ and Others: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of lids.com™ and hatworld.com™, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  * With Your Consent: Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

How secure is information about me?  ( [Top](http://www.lids.com/privacy_policy.html#top) )  
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Thawte certified Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.

We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.  
  
What information can I access?  ( [Top](http://www.lids.com/privacy_policy.html#top) )  
lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ gives you access to the following information about you for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. This list will change as our Web site evolves.

Order Tracking - Gives you the ability to track orders and view order history. To access your Order Tracking information, click on the "My Account" link in the top portion of the site.

Account Information - Once you have logged in, you may access and update your account information by clicking on "My Account" displayed on the top of every page.  
  
What choices do I have?  ( [Top](http://www.lids.com/privacy_policy.html#top) )  
As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase.

You can add or update certain information on pages such as those listed in the "My Account" section above. When you update information, your old information is replaced by your new information.

If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please notify us by sending an e-mail to [contactus@hatworld.com](mailto:contactus@hatworld.com).

If you do not want to receive Conditions of Use and other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still govern your use of lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.

The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

The Federal Trade Commission provides useful information about online privacy on its own Web site, Site Seeing on the Internet.  
  
Do lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ collect information from children?  ( [Top](http://www.lids.com/privacy_policy.html#top) )  
lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ do not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ only with involvement of a parent or guardian.  
What are the conditions of use, notices, and revisions for the lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ web site?  ( [Top](http://www.lids.com/privacy_policy.html#top) )  
If you choose to visit lids.com™ and hatworld.com™, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Indiana. If you have any concern about privacy at lids.com™ and hatworld.com™, please send us a thorough description to [contactus@hatworld.com](mailto:contactus@hatworld.com), and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.  
What are my lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ bill of rights?  ( [Top](http://www.lids.com/privacy_policy.html#top) )  
  
  1. We guarantee that every transaction you make at lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ will be safe. This means that you pay nothing, if unauthorized charges are made to your card as a result of shopping at lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ subject to the details of this policy, which are posted [here](http://www.lids.com/privacy_policy.html/#guarantee). Read the details of this policy. Plus, you'll be one of thousands of customers who have safely shopped with us without credit card fraud. If you feel more comfortable, you may call us and order by phone.
  2. No obligation. You are under no obligation to buy anything.
  3. Unsubscribing. You can unsubscribe or change your subscription to any of our Personal Notification Services at any time.

What is the lids.com™ and hatworld.com™ fraud prevention statement?  ( [Top](http://www.lids.com/privacy_policy.html#top) )  
LIDS, HATWORLD and THE HAT ZONE are concerned with the protection and privacy of all of our customers. To ensure your online shopping experience is the best it can be we have implemented procedures to safeguard against fraud. To protect our customers from the high price of fraud, Hat World, Corp. reserves the right to verify any order for fraud prevention purposes. This may result in delays to Next Day and 2nd Day Air orders. All orders will be researched within 24 hours. If we are unable to verify order information within 48 hours, the order will be cancelled. Hat World, Corp. is working to protect our customers from the high cost of fraud so that we can continue to provide a large inventory of competitively priced products and a positive online shopping experience for you, our customer.  

|  |   
|    
CUSTOMER CARE DEPARTMENT: Open 24 hours a day, 7 days a week. Call us toll-free at 1-888-564-HATS(4287)  
  
© 2007 LIDS, Genesco. All Rights Reserved.
